Guide to the Andrew Dickson White papers, 1832-1919.
White, Andrew Dickson papers, 1832-1919
- Series I. Correspondence
  - Undescribed, November 5, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 4)
    Wedding Invitation. Two copies
  - J.C. Schwab, November 4, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - D.C. Gilman, November 4, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 4)
    Letter. Addressed to Dr. Hoyt
  - Frederick White, November 4, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - Metropolitan Museum of Art, November 4, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 4)
    Invitation. 29th Annual Exhibition, Autumn Reception
  - Andrew Dickson White, November 4, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 4)
    Letter. Addressed to H.W. Sage; clocktower inscription; three pages
  - Theodore W. Koch, November 4, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 4)
    Letter. Enclosed: article
  - Juliet J.P. Hill, November 5, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - John W. Hoyt, November 5, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - Anne Edward Foster, November 5, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - Herbert B. Adams, November 5, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 4)
    Postcard. American Historical Association
  - Cornell University Registrar (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - Andrews Bros., November 5, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - Mrs. Leland Stamford, November 5, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - Thomas R. Slicer, November 5, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - Park & Tilford, November 6, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Mrs. John Paulding Filer, November 6, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - William C. Phillips, November 6, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - G. Brown Goode, November 7, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Clara White; Spencer B. Newberry, November 7, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Frederick White, November 7, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Clarence Tucker, November 7, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - J.M. Scott, November 7, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - H.W. Sage, November 8, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - A.W., November 8, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Stewart L. Woodford, November 8, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Thomas R. Slicer, November 9, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Katherine W. Hewett, November 10, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Frederick White, November 10, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - R.S. Hyer, November 11, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Mrs. George B. Leonard, November 11, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Sarah M. Cage, November 11, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Andrew Dickson White, November 11, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Andrew Dickson White, November 11, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Frederick White, November 11, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Jeremiah Zimmerman, November 11, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Andrew Carnegie, November 12, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - J.H. Crooker, November 12, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - Rev. A.J. Evans, November 12, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 6)
    Letter. Church of the Immaculate Conception
  - E.D. Moses, November 12, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - E.D. Moses, November 12, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 6)
    Letter. Enclosed: letter to Clark Bell
  - The Morning News, November 11, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 6)
    Newspaper Article. "Mr. Bayard on Socialism"
  - The Morning News, October 20, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 6)
    Newspaper Article. "The Coming Crisis"
  - The Morning News (Box 73, Folder 6)
    Letter. "Social and Economic Unit at Sugar Grove"
  - The Morning News (Box 73, Folder 6)
    Letter. "A Workingmen's Movement"
  - Andrew Dickson White, November 12, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 6)
    Letter. Addressed to Elizabeth E. Evans; three pages
  - Andrew Dickson White, November 12, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - Frederick White, November 12, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - Helen Magill White, November 12, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - Ashley W. Cole, November 14, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - Juliet L.P. Hill, November 14, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - Frank H. Chase, November 14, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - Mary J. Jackson, November 14, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - Joel Munsell's Sons, November 14, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - H.L. Wayland, November 14, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - Bellows, November 15, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - Mary Tuttle, November 15, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - Clara White Newberry, November 15, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - Gardiner G. Hubbard, November 15, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - John W. Hoyt, November 16, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 7)
    Letter. Enclosed: pg. 9-10, National University
  - Albert Shaw, November 16, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - C.O. Shephard, November 16, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - Simon Wolf, November 16, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - Frederick White, November 16, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - F.B. Sanborn, November 18, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - Andrew Dickson White, November 18, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - Helen Magill White, November 18, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - Ithaca Conservatory of Music, November 19, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - R.B. Howland, November 19, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - John W. Hoyt, November 19, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - Clara White Newberry, November 19, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - Frederick White, November 19, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - Frederick White, November 19, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - Clara White Newberry, November 20, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - C.G. Peterson, November 20, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - Clarence Tucker, November 20, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - Andrew Dickson White, November 20, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 8)
    Letter. Addressed to Mrs. Tuttle; two pages
  - Andrew Dickson White, November 20, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - Hitchcock, Darling, & Co., November 21, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - Oscar S. Straus, November 21, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - Andrew Dickson White, November 21, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 8)
    Letter. Addressed to A.W. Bishop
  - Andrew Dickson White, November 21, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - R.L. Guion, November 22, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - Caroline, November 22, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - Juliet L.P. Hill, November 22, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - Andrew Dickson White, November 22, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 8)
    Letter. Addressed to D.C. Gilman; three pages
  - Andrew Dickson White, November 22, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - Frederick White, November 22, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - Theodore Bacon, November 23, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - A.W. Bishop, November 23, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - Elizabeth E. Evans, November 23, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - D.C. Gilman, November 25, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - William W. Green, November 25, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 9)
    Letter. Enclosed: "Thanksgiving" by William W. Green
  - Barbara F. Schurman, November 25, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - Henry T. Allen, November 26, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - Frederick William Holls, November 26, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - Frederick White, November 26, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - Burt G. Wilder, November 26, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - R.L. Guion, November 27, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - Frederick White, November 27, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - Ward, November 28, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - German American Society, November 28, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 9)
    Rules.
  - Hitchcock, Darling, & Co., November 28, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - Andrew Dickson White, November 28, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - Lewis R. Harley, November 29, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - Juliet L.P. Hill, November 29, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - Andrew Dickson White, November 29, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - Andrew Dickson White, November 29, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - Frederick White, November 29, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - Andrew Dickson White, November 30, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - Frederika B.F., November 1895 (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - Juliet L.P. Hill, December 1, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - Willard Fiske, December 2, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - W.E. Greenswalt, December 2, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - David J. Hill, December 2, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - David J. Hill, December 2, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - John W. Hoyt, December 2, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - Sarah W. Magill, December 2, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - Clarence Tucker, December 2, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - Frederick White, December 2, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - J.H. Crooker, December 3, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - H., December 3, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - Juliet L.P. Hill, December 3, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - Macedon Academy, December 3, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - Onondaga Historical Association, December 3, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 10)
    Donation Acknowledgement.
  - C.O. Shephard, December 3, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - Andrew Dickson White, December 3, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 10)
    Letter. Addressed to Goldwin Smith; three pages
  - Andrew Dickson White, December 3, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - Andrew Dickson White, December 3, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - Andrew Dickson White, December 4, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 11)
    Letter. Addressed to the Board of Trustees
  - S.R. C., December 4, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 11)
  - Andrew Dickson White, December 4, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 11)
  - Andrew Dickson White, December 4, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 11)
  - Frederick White, December 4, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 11)
  - Frederick White, December 5, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 11)
  - Marcia Andrews, December 6, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 11)
  - Smithsonian Institution, December 6, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 11)
  - T.R. Lounsbury, December 6, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 11)
  - The Rochester Clearing House Association, December 6, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 11)
  - Goldwin Smith, December 6, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 11)
  - Undescribed, December 7, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 11)
    Newspaper Clip. "Andrew D. White Addressed the Civic Body, Received with Cheers"
  - Charles P. Ford, December 7, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 11)
    Letter. Rochester Chamber of Commerce
  - R.L. Guion, December 7, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 11)
  - David J. Hill, December 7, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 11)
  - Hiram W. Sibley, December 7, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 11)
  - Goldwin Smith, December 7, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 11)
  - Max Lansbury, December 8, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 12)
  - Herbert B. Adams, December 9, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 12)
    Letter. American Historical Association
  - Andrew Dickson White, December 9, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 12)
    Letter. Addressed to T.R. Lounsbury; two pages
  - Andrew Dickson White, December 9, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 12)
  - Frederick White, December 9, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 12)
  - American Historical Association, December 10, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 12)
  - Juliet L.P. Hill, December 10, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 12)
  - Caroline Roberts, December 10, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 12)
  - Andrew Dickson White, December 10, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 12)
  - Herman M. Biggs, December 11, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 12)
  - T.R. Lounsbury, December 11, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 12)
  - Frederick White, December 11, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 12)
  - Herbert B. Adams, December 11, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 12)
  - Clara White Newberry, December 12, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 12)
  - Andrew Dickson White, December 12, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 12)
    Letter. Addressed to Professor and Mrs. Evans; four pages
  - R.L. Guion, December 14, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 12)
  - Public Education Association, December 1895 (Box 73, Folder 12)
    Winter Course Catalog.
  - Stephen S. Burt, December 15, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 13)
  - J. Laurence Laughlin, December 15, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 13)
    Letter. Political Economy Club
  - Horace Walpole, December 15, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 13)
  - Gardiner G. Hubbard, December 16, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 13)
  - Frederick White, December 16, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 13)
  - Frank S. Gardner, December 17, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 13)
    Letter. New York Board of Trade and Transportation
  - William P., December 17, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 13)
  - H.A. Richmond, December 17, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 13)
  - Andrew Dickson White, December 18, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 13)
    Letter. Addressed to Mrs. E.P. Evans
  - George Priest, December 18, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 13)
  - H.A. Richmond, December 18, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 13)
  - F.B. Sanborn, December 18, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 13)
  - Taylor, December 18, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 13)
  - Andrew Dickson White, December 18, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 13)
  - Andrew Dickson White, December 18, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 13)
  - Clifton R. Breckinridge, December 19, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 13)
  - Mr. & Mrs. Cross, December 19, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 13)
  - W. Harris, December 19, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 13)
  - B.L. Whitman, December 19, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 13)
  - Leonard Woolsey Bacon, December 20, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 14)
    Letter. National Armenian Relief Committee
  - Herman M. Biggs, December 21, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 14)
  - Frederick William Holls, December 21, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 14)
  - Theodore F. S., December 21, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 14)
  - C.O. Shephard, December 21, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 14)
  - Clarence Tucker, December 21, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 14)
  - J. Gale Needham, December 22, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 14)
  - M.M. S., December 22, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 14)
  - Frederick White, December 22, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 14)
  - Andrew Carnegie, December 23, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 14)
  - William Seymour E., December 23, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 14)
  - The Troy Daily Times, December 23, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 14)
  - Thomas Fletcher Fullard, December 24, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 14)
  - Frederick White, December 24, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 14)
  - Julius Chambers, December 25, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 14)
  - John W. Hoyt, December 25, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 14)
  - Clara White Newberry, December 25, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 14)
  - Henry T. Allen, December 26, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 15)
  - R. P., December 26, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 15)
  - Frederick White, December 26, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 15)
  - S.L. W., December 26, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 15)
  - Lewis R. Harley, December 27, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 15)
  - Morris Jastrow, December 27, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 15)
  - W.E.H. Lecky, December 27, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 15)
  - Andrew White Newberry, December 27, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 15)
  - Spencer B. Newberry, December 27, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 15)
  - C.O. Shephard, December 27, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 15)
  - Gustav H. Schwab, December 27, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 15)
  - Robert Stein, December 27, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 15)
    Letter. Enlosed: two New York Tribune clippings; three pages
  - Andrew Dickson White, December 27, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 15)
    Letter. Addressed to the President
  - F.B. Sanborn, December 28, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 15)
  - Charles E. Waters, December 28, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 15)
  - Clara White Newberry, December 29, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 15)
  - Frederick White, December 30, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 15)
  - F. Wayland Fellowes, December 31, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 15)
  - Edward A. R., December 31, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 15)
  - Henry S., December 31, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 15)
  - John W. Hoyt, December 1895 (Box 73, Folder 15)
  - George Lincoln Burr, December 1895 (Box 73, Folder 15)
  - Mary M. Adams, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 16)
    Poem. "The Message of the Dead"
  - Beatrice Magill, 1895 (Box 73, Folder 16)
  - W.E. Greenswalt, January 1, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 17)
  - H.H. Blanchard, January 1, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 17)
  - Marcia Andrews, January 2, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 17)
  - Henry B. Blackwell, January 2, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 17)
  - David J. Brewer, January 2, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 17)
  - Julius Chambers, January 2, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 17)
  - J. Edward Clarke, January 2, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 17)
  - E. F., January 2, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 17)
  - Charles H. Adams, January 2, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 17)
  - George Coleman, January 2, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 17)
  - T.F. Davis, January 2, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 17)
  - Edwin Emerson, January 2, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 17)
  - Fellowes, January 2, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 17)
  - J.C. Hendrix, January 2, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 17)
  - Frederick William Holls, January 2, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 17)
  - John W. Hoyt, January 2, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 17)
  - William Preston G., January 2, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 17)
  - Leslie Weekly, January 2, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 17)
  - Editor, Library Digest, January 2, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 17)
  - Henry Romeike, January 2, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 17)
    Newspaper Clip. Four pages
  - John N. Ostrom, January 2, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 17)
  - The Press Clipping Bureau, January 2, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 17)
  - Putnam, January 2, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 17)
  - T.E. Roessle, January 2, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 17)
  - C.O. Shephard, January 2, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 17)
  - C.O. Shephard, January 2, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 17)
  - T. Guilford Smith, January 2, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 17)
  - Homer B. Sprague, January 2, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 17)
  - Andrew Dickson White, January 2, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 17)
  - Andrew Strong White, January 2, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 17)
  - Frederick White, January 2, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 17)
  - Undescribed, January 2, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 17)
  - Undescribed, January 2, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 17)
  - N.W. Cady, January 3, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 18)
  - M.W. Cass, January 3, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 18)
  - Edwin Emerson, January 3, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 18)
  - J.W. Fiske, January 3, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 18)
  - Simon H. Gage, January 3, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 18)
  - Gardiner G. Hubbard, January 3, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 18)
  - Charles E. Hughes, January 3, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 18)
  - Ralph Lee, January 3, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 18)
  - Richard M. Mitchell, January 3, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 18)
  - Theodore T. Munger, January 3, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 18)
  - R. P., January 3, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 18)
  - Herbert H.D. Peirce, January 3, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 18)
  - Henry W. Sage, January 3, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 18)
  - E.G. Benedict, January 3, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 18)
  - Issac H. Taylor, January 3, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 18)
  - Issac H. Taylor, January 3, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 18)
  - Clarence Tucker, January 3, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 18)
  - George P. Upton, January 3, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 18)
    Letter. The Chicago Tribune
  - Undescribed, January 3, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 18)
  - Henry Randall Waite, January 3, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 18)
    Letter. American Institute of Civics
  - C. Bradley Warner, January 3, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 18)
  - Undescribed, January 3, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 18)
  - Frederick White, January 3, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 18)
  - Carroll D. Wright, January 3, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 18)
  - Edward Allen, January 4, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 19)
  - David J. Brewer, January 4, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 19)
  - David J. Brewer, January 4, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 19)
  - The Clasp Envelope Co., January 4, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 19)
  - Louis Friedman, January 4, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 19)
  - D.C. Gilman, January 4, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 19)
  - John N. H., January 4, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 19)
  - George Lincoln Burr, January 4, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 19)
    Letter. Enclosed: letter from Mrs. Tuttle
  - J.M. Scott, January 4, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 19)
  - C.E. Smith, January 4, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 19)
  - Robert Stein, January 4, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 19)
    Letter. Twelve pages
  - Andrew Dickson White, January 4, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 19)
    Telegram. Addressed to D.C. Gilman
  - Andrew Dickson White, January 4, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 19)
  - Andrew Dickson White, January 4, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 19)
    Letter. Addressed to Henry W. Sage
  - Andrew Dickson White, January 4, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 19)
  - Undescribed, January 4, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 19)
  - Gardiner G. Hubbard, January 5, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 19)
  - I.H. Butterfield, January 6, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 20)
  - Charles Diedrich, January 6, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 20)
  - J. Walter Blandford, January 6, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 20)
    Letter. Enclosed: Department of State proceedings
  - Clara White White, January 6, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 20)
  - Arthur Rakestraw, January 6, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 20)
  - James M. Ruso, January 6, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 20)
  - Smalley, January 6, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 20)
  - Charles Tucker, January 6, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 20)
  - G.W. Smalley, January 6, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 20)
  - John Wanamaker, January 6, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 20)
  - Frederick White, January 6, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 20)
  - Henry J. White, January 6, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 20)
  - L.O. Howard, January 7, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 20)
  - Daniel S. Lamont, January 7, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 20)
  - A.C. Sea, January 7, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 20)
  - Henry C. Potter, January 7, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 20)
  - Goldwin Smith, January 7, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 20)
  - Issac H. Taylor, January 7, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 20)
  - George R. Van de Water, January 7, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 20)
    Letter. Enclosed: letter
  - John Wanamaker, January 7, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 20)
  - S.P. Langley, January 8, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 21)
  - Carl Evans Boyd, January 8, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 21)
  - H.A. Richmond, January 8, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 21)
  - Andrew Dickson White, January 8, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 21)
  - F.W. Fullard, January 9, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 21)
  - Herbert J. Hagerman, January 9, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 21)
  - Charles E. Hughes, January 9, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 21)
  - Mary Song, January 9, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 21)
  - James M. Ruso, January 9, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 21)
  - Smalley, January 9, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 21)
  - Helen Magill White, January 9, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 21)
  - T.F. Davis, January 10, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 21)
  - Undescribed, January 10, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 21)
  - Louis A. Dent, January 10, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 21)
  - Lamont, January 10, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 21)
  - Undescribed, January 10, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 21)
  - F.B. Sanborn, January 10, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 21)
  - George P. Upton, January 10, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 21)
  - Horace White, January 10, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 21)
  - C.K. Adams, January 11, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 22)
  - C.F. Allen, January 11, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 22)
  - Charles E. Hall, January 11, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 22)
  - Mary Henderson, January 11, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 22)
  - T.F. Crane, January 12, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 22)
  - G.A. Benton, January 13, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 22)
  - George Lincoln Burr, January 13, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 22)
  - Dodge Pickering, January 13, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 22)
  - Willard Fiske, January 13, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 22)
  - T.R. Lounsbury, January 13, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 22)
  - George L. Maris, January 13, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 22)
  - Issac H. Taylor, January 13, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 22)
  - Andrew Dickson White, January 13, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 22)
  - Undescribed, January 13, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 22)
  - Ball, January 14, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 22)
  - F.A. Blades, January 14, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 22)
  - Noah Davis, January 14, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 22)
  - Frank S. Gardener, January 14, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 22)
  - Frederick William Holls, January 14, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 22)
  - Mary Song, January 14, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 22)
  - Edwin F., January 14, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 22)
  - Andrew Dickson White, January 14, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 22)
  - Maria Donaldson, January 15, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 23)
  - Undescribed, January 15, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 23)
    Letter. Musical Auditorium architectural plans
  - E.R. J., January 15, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 23)
  - Theodore T. Munger, January 15, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 23)
  - Undescribed, January 15, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 23)
    Letter. Natural Science Association of America
  - Charles P. Daly, January 16, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 24)
  - David J. Brewer, January 16, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 24)
  - George Lincoln Burr, January 16, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 24)
  - F.W. Elwood, January 16, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 24)
  - A.C. Sea, January 16, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 24)
  - Oscar S. Straus, January 16, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 24)
  - Oscar S. Straus, January 16, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 24)
  - Ward, January 16, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 24)
  - Andrew Dickson White, January 16, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 24)
  - Yale Alumni Association, January 16, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 24)
  - Undescribed, January 17, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 24)
  - Robert Stein, January 17, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 24)
  - Andrew Dickson White, January 17, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 24)
    Lettter. Addressed to George Lincoln Burr; two pages
  - Frederick White, January 17, 1896 (Box 73, Folder 24)